

CONTACT ME



918-361-8479



mstesney12@gmail.com



201East Huntsville Rd Fayetteville, AR 72701

SOCIAL

www.linkedin.com/in/mark-stesney



www.github.com/markstez05

PRO SKILLS

FRONTEND

• React

Redux

BootStrap

• HTML

SASS/CSS

BACKEND

Node.js

Express

MongoDB

Django

LANGUAGES

JavaScript

C++

Python

MARK STESNEY

full stack web developer | project manager | creator

My skills include full stack web development as well as supervising and facilitating multi-faceted projects, troubleshooting an array of technological issues, managing and developing groups of people, orchestrating positive client experiences, and engaging in constructive analysis and feedback.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Treatment Services, LLC

Chief Development Officer

2015 - 2017

Worked with State Opiod Treatment Authority to determine statistical relevance of areas in need of treatment facilities. Researched and surveyed potential clinic locations. Established community relationships to generate awareness and educate around the stigma of and need for treatment facilities. Facilitated all lease and facility contract negotiations. Managed site construction. Worked with the D.E.A. to schedule and complete licensing and certifications.

Office Manager

2010 - 2015

Conducted recruitment, interviewing, hiring, and training of new staff and team expansion. Organized and lead staff meetings. Supported employee development through individual guidance meetings. Engineered strategies to increase office efficiency and patient satisfaction. Provided troubleshooting and repair for office computer hardware and software. Installed, updated, and trained staff on clinical software. Managed network facility and maintained network security. Maintained office inventory and managed clinic medical supplies. Maintained patient rapport and care in a high-stress environment through skillful empathy and de-escalation practices while managing day to day tasks.

Administrative Assistant

2007 - 2010

Promoted positive patient care and experience. Facilitated new patient intake and guidance through policy and procedure. Managed daily high-volume cash transactions and deposits. Maintained precise accounting spreadsheets and tracked daily budget reports. Organized and conducted patient accounts payable and communication.

EDUCATION

Lambda School 🔯

Full Stack Development & Computer Science

2018

Completed Lambdas six month Computer Science and Software Engineering course consisting of an immersive hands-on curriculum with a focus on computer science, software engineering, and web development. Coded in several different languages (including JavaScript, Python, and C) and learned computing from its most fundamental levels.

- Pair Programming
- Peer Code Review
- Daily Standup Meetings
- Time Retrospective Forms

REFERENCES

Alan Jamieson: CEO
TREATMENT SERVICES, LLC
ALAN@OKTREATMENT.COM
1.918.346.4258

 Angie Leek: MA, LMFT HOLO COUNSELING ANGIE.LEEK.MFT@GMAIL.COM 1.479.668.3688 Marcus Montgomery: OWNER MONTGOMERY PRODUCTIONS MONTGOMERY.MARCUS.86@GMAIL.COM 1.918.520.9256